{
    "subject": "resource/David_Baulcombe",
    "predicate": "ontology/award",
    "object": "resource/Royal_Society",
    "human_readable": "David Baulcombe was awarded by the Royal Society.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9649193286895752,
            "question": "In what field did David Baulcombe receive recognition from the Royal Society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9634506702423096,
            "question": "Why was David Baulcombe awarded by the Royal Society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.891406238079071,
            "question": "Who was awarded by the Royal Society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7111722230911255,
            "question": "What prestigious organization awarded David Baulcombe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6697415113449097,
            "question": "Are there other notable individuals who have been awarded by the Royal Society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5959810018539429,
            "question": "What is David Baulcombe known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5438997745513916,
            "question": "What is the significance of receiving an award from the Royal Society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49683383107185364,
            "question": "What other achievements has David Baulcombe accomplished besides this award?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4785405993461609,
            "question": "How does this award impact David Baulcombe's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46888113021850586,
            "question": "What are some of the criteria for receiving an award from the Royal Society?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=David Baulcombe was awarded by the Royal Society.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6382_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does this award impact David Baulcombe's career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6382_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other achievements has David Baulcombe accomplished besides this award?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6382_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of receiving an award from the Royal Society?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6382_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6382_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6382_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6382_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6382_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6382_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6382_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6382_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6382_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6382_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6382_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Sir David Baulcombe received the Royal Medal from the Royal Society in 2006, among other awards and recognitions. Therefore, the statement that David Baulcombe was awarded by the Royal Society is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}